Finding aid to Office of the President William Allan Neilson files CA.MS.00013
Smith College Archives
- Series I. Correspondence
  - Gallagher, H. Clifford and Edith W., 1918-31 (Box 373, Folder 13)
  - Gamble, Cecil H., 1926-39 (Box 373, Folder 14)
  - Ganong, William Francis, 1918-37 (Box 373, Folder 15-16)
  - Garber, Mary Jane, 1920-37 (Box 373, Folder 17)
  - Gardiner, Harry Norman, 1917-34 (Box 373, Folder 18)
  - Gardner, William G., 1926-29 (Box 373, Folder 19)
  - Garrison, Eleanor '04, 1927-28 (Box 373, Folder 20)
  - Garrison, Mabel, 1934-39; undated (Box 373, Folder 21)
  - Gavit, John Palmer, 1922-38 (Box 373, Folder 22)
  - Ge (misc), 1920-39; undated (Box 373, Folder 23)
  - Genung, Elizabeth Faith, 1919-36 (Box 373, Folder 24)
  - Gi (misc), 1923-39; undated (Box 373, Folder 25)
  - Gibbons, Lois Oliphant, 1920-28 (Box 373, Folder 26)
  - Gibson, James Jerome, 1935-39 (Box 373, Folder 27)
  - Gifford, Rosamond, 1937-38 (Box 373, Folder 28)
  - Gilbreth, Lillian M., 1924-32 (Box 373, Folder 29)
  - Gilchrist, Marie E., 1930-35 (Box 373, Folder 30)
  - Gildersleeve, Virginia C., 1921-39 (Box 373, Folder 31)
  - Gilkey, Charles W., 1928-34 (Box 373, Folder 32)
  - Gill, Bessie Faunce '87, 1921-29 (Box 373, Folder 33)
  - Gill, Emily F. Abbey, 1935-37 (Box 373, Folder 34)
  - Gillett, Arthur L., 1919-31 (Box 373, Folder 35)
  - Gilman, Florence, 1917-39 (Box 373, Folder 36)
  - Gilmore, Robert C., 1932-37 (Box 373, Folder 37)
  - Giorni, Aurelio, 1936-39 (Box 373, Folder 38)
  - Gl (misc), 1919-39; undated (Box 373, Folder 39)
  - Glasgow, Robert and Louise C., 1919-20 (Box 373, Folder 40)
  - Glass, Meta, 1928-36 (Box 373, Folder 41)
  - Gleason, Emily (Clapp) '16, 1936-39 (Box 373, Folder 42)
  - Go (misc), 1920-39; undated (Box 374, Folder 1)
  - Goldthwait, Joel E., 1918-35 (Box 374, Folder 2)
  - Goode, Blanche, 1918-21 (Box 374, Folder 3)
  - Goodman, William W., 1935-37 (Box 374, Folder 4)
  - Goodnow, Catherine S., 1936-37 (Box 374, Folder 5)
  - Goodwin, Sarah S., 1919-36 (Box 374, Folder 6)
  - Gordon, Cyrus H., 1938-39 (Box 374, Folder 7)
  - Gorokhoff, Ivan Timofeevitch, 1918-35 (Box 374, Folder 8)
  - Gragg, Florence Alden, 1917-39 (Box 374, Folder 9)
  - Gra (misc), 1919-36; undated (Box 374, Folder 10)
  - Grant, Elihu, 1928-34 (Box 374, Folder 11)
  - Grant, Elliott Mansfield, 1921-39 (Box 374, Folder 12)
  - Grant, Madeleine Parker, 1930-33 (Box 374, Folder 13)
  - Grant, William, 1925-27 (Box 374, Folder 14)
  - Gre (misc), 1920-39; undated (Box 374, Folder 15)
  - Greene, Helen French, 1918-38 (Box 374, Folder 16)
  - Greene, John Morton, 1917-18 (Box 374, Folder 17)
  - Greenlaw, Edwin, 1917-21 (Box 374, Folder 18)
  - Greever, Garland, 1920-32 (Box 374, Folder 19)
  - Gri-Grz (misc), 1923-42 (Box 374, Folder 20)
  - Grierson, Herbert J. C., 1924-38; undated (Box 374, Folder 21)
  - Griffin, Nathaniel E., 1921-38 (Box 374, Folder 22)
  - Grosbayne, Benjamin, 1925-1936 (Box 374, Folder 23)
  - Gu-Gz (misc), 1918-39; undated (Box 374, Folder 24)
  - Guiet, Jeanne Seigneur and Rene, 1930-38 (Box 374, Folder 25)
  - Guion, Ellen (Larmore) '97, 1919-28 (Box 374, Folder 26)
  - Guilloton, Madeleine and Vincent, 1930-39 (Box 374, Folder 27)
  - Gunn, Sidney, 1922-28 (Box 374, Folder 28)
  - Gushee, Vera Marie, 1925-36 (Box 374, Folder 29)
  - Haa-Hal (misc), 1920-40; undated (Box 374, Folder 30)
  - Hadley, Ruth (Canedy) '02, 1928-36 (Box 374, Folder 31)
  - Hagedorn, Hermann, 1929-37 (Box 374, Folder 32)
  - Hale, Richard W., 1929-36 (Box 374, Folder 33)
  - Hall, Christine, 1919-22 (Box 374, Folder 34)
  - Hall, Leland, 1920-41 (Box 374, Folder 35)
  - Halle, Rita S., 1928-29 (Box 374, Folder 36)
  - Halpern, George E., 1930 (Box 374, Folder 37)
  - Ham (misc), 1913-39 (Box 374, Folder 38)
  - Hamill, Alice Noble and Emmy Lou '37, 1935 (Box 374, Folder 39)
  - Hamilton, Edith, 1919-27 (Box 374, Folder 40)
  - Hamilton, Mary E., 1929 (Box 374, Folder 41)
  - Hamilton, Sarah Hook, 1923-39 (Box 374, Folder 42)
  - Hamm, Elizabeth (Creevey) '05, 1918-36 (Box 374, Folder 43)
  - Han-Hap (misc), 1922-39; undated (Box 375, Folder 1)
  - Hankins, Frank Hamilton, 1922-41 (Box 375, Folder 2-16)
  - Hanna, Mary Stuart, 1928; undated (Box 375, Folder 17)
  - Hanscom, Elizabeth Deering, 1917-37 (Box 375, Folder 18)
  - Hapgood, Norman, 1926-37 (Box 375, Folder 19)
  - Hara-Harr (misc), 1918-39; undated (Box 375, Folder 20)
  - Harano, Kiyo, 1927-28 (Box 375, Folder 21)
  - Harlow, Samuel Ralph, 1922-39; undated (Box 375, Folder 22)
  - Harper, Roland M., 1932-36 (Box 375, Folder 23)
  - Harrower, Mary Rachel, 1928-34 (Box 375, Folder 24)
  - Hart (misc), 1921-37; undated (Box 375, Folder 25)
  - Hart, Anne B. G., 1923-38 (Box 375, Folder 26)
  - Hart, Walter Morris, 1920-27 (Box 375, Folder 27)
  - Hartwell, Kathleen E., 1922-33 (Box 375, Folder 28)
  - Harv-Haz (misc), 1920-39; undated (Box 375, Folder 29)
  - Hastings, Mary E., 1926-28 (Box 375, Folder 30)
  - Hatch, Laura, 1920; undated (Box 375, Folder 31)
  - Hause, Nathan E., 1922-23 (Box 375, Folder 32)
  - He (misc), 1919-40; undated (Box 376, Folder 1)
  - Heine, Aida Agnes, 1927-37 (Box 376, Folder 2)
  - Helgesson, Uno Helmer, 1932-39 (Box 376, Folder 3)
  - Helm, Wilbur, 1925-26 (Box 376, Folder 4)
  - Herrington, H. W., 1925-29 (Box 376, Folder 5)
  - Herron, Rosalind (Hubbell) '23, 1931-39 (Box 376, Folder 6)
  - Hi (misc), 1919-39; undated (Box 376, Folder 7)
  - Hibbitt, George W. and Marian T., 1933-35 (Box 376, Folder 8)
  - Hicks, Granville, 1929-35 (Box 376, Folder 9)
  - Hildt, John Coffey, 1918-1838 (Box 376, Folder 10)
  - Hilka, Alfons, 1930 (Box 376, Folder 11)
  - Hill, Charles Jarvis, 1931-39 (Box 376, Folder 12)
  - Hill, Justina Hamilton '16, 1935; undated (Box 376, Folder 13)
  - Hill, William C., 1927-44 (Box 376, Folder 14)
  - Hills, Helen (Hills) '08, 1924-35 (Box 376, Folder 15)
  - Hincks, Sarah, 1922-29 (Box 376, Folder 16)
  - Hiss, Philip, 1931-32 (Box 376, Folder 17)
  - Hoa-Hok (misc), 1922-37; undated (Box 376, Folder 18)
  - Hocking, William E., 1927-36 (Box 376, Folder 19)
  - Hockridge, Erwin F., 1928 (Box 376, Folder 20)
  - Hodder, Margery Knight '34, 1934 (Box 376, Folder 21)
  - Hofer, Philip, 1936-39 (Box 376, Folder 22)
  - Hoffman, Jane, 1934-35 (Box 376, Folder 23)
  - Hol-Hoo (misc), 1920-39 (Box 376, Folder 24)
  - Holbrook, Marguerite Francis '33, 1933-36 (Box 376, Folder 25)
  - Holcombe, Arthur N., 1933-35 (Box 376, Folder 26)
  - Holden, H. Mildred, 1930-40 (Box 376, Folder 27)
  - Holmes, John Haynes, 1919-32 (Box 376, Folder 28)
  - Holmes, Robert, 1925-29 (Box 376, Folder 29)
  - Holmes, Rebecca Wilder, 1919-38; undated (Box 376, Folder 30)
  - Homer, Louise, 1931-32 (Box 376, Folder 31)
  - Hooker, Richard, 1920-27 (Box 376, Folder 32)
  - Hoover, Herbert, 1917-28 (Box 376, Folder 33)
  - Hop-Hou (misc), 1918-41; undated (Box 376, Folder 34)
  - Hopkins, Ernest M., 1921-38 (Box 376, Folder 35)
  - Hopkins, Mary Murray, 1917-21 (Box 376, Folder 36)
  - Hopkinson, Charles S., 1923-35; undated (Box 376, Folder 37)
  - Hornbeak, Katherine Gee, 1931-39 (Box 376, Folder 38)
  - Horton, David, 1929-31 (Box 376, Folder 39)
  - Houghton, Alanson B., 1932-33 (Box 376, Folder 40)
  - Houghton Mifflin Company, 1923-25 (Box 376, Folder 41)
  - Houpt, Wilber E., 1927 (Box 376, Folder 42)
  - Houston, John A., 1919-29 (Box 376, Folder 43)
  - Hov-Hoz (misc), 1918-41; undated (Box 376, Folder 44)
  - Howe, William D., 1925-36 (Box 376, Folder 45)
  - Hu-Hy (misc), 1918-41; undated (Box 377, Folder 1)
  - Hubbard, Grace A. '87, 1918-28 (Box 377, Folder 2)
  - Hubert, C. Elizabeth (Baldwin) '23, 1931-35 (Box 377, Folder 3)
  - Hughes, Frona (Brooks) '22, 1934-36 (Box 377, Folder 4)
  - Hull, Cordell, 1939-44 (Box 377, Folder 5)
  - Hunt, Agnes '97, 1918-25 (Box 377, Folder 6)
  - Hunt, Nathan P., 1923-30 (Box 377, Folder 7)
  - Huntington, Frances (Carpenter) '12, 1932-39 (Box 377, Folder 8)
  - Husserl, Gerhert, 1930-39 (Box 377, Folder 9)
  - Hutchins, Robert M., 1923-37 (Box 377, Folder 10)
  - Hutchinson, Virginia (Mellen) '00, 1924-27 (Box 377, Folder 11)
  - Hyde, George Palmer, 1923-37 (Box 377, Folder 12)
  - I (misc), 1924-39 (Box 377, Folder 13)
  - Imbault-Huart, Yvonne; 1926-38 (Box 377, Folder 14)
  - Israel, Harold Edward, 1937-39 (Box 377, Folder 15)
  - Ja (misc), 1918-38; undated (Box 377, Folder 16)
  - Jacob, Cary Franklin, 1928-39 (Box 377, Folder 17)
  - Jacobi, Frederick and Irene, 1934-39 (Box 377, Folder 18)
  - James, Henry, 1923-30 (Box 377, Folder 19)
  - Je (misc), 1922-39; undated (Box 377, Folder 20)
  - Jo-Joh (misc), 1922-39; undated (Box 377, Folder 21)
  - Johnson, Edith Norse, 1920-28 (Box 377, Folder 22)
  - Johnson, Eleanor Hope '94, 1918-27; undated (Box 377, Folder 23)
  - Johnson, Frances (Smith) '20, 1936 (Box 377, Folder 24)
  - Jon-Joz (misc), 1917-40; undated (Box 377, Folder 25)
  - Jones, Arthur Taber, 1920-39 (Box 377, Folder 26)
  - Jones, Frederic Marshall, 1920-39 (Box 377, Folder 27)
  - Jordan, Elsie F. Pratt, 1924-27 (Box 377, Folder 28)
  - Jordan, Mary Augusta, 1918-32 (Box 377, Folder 29-30)
  - Josten, Werner, 1923-38 (Box 377, Folder 31)
  - Ju (misc), 1921-38 (Box 377, Folder 32)
  - Ka (misc), 1920-39; undated (Box 377, Folder 33)
  - Kallen, Horace M., 1927-36 (Box 377, Folder 34)
  - Kane, Florence (Ward) '17 and T. L., 1920-38 (Box 377, Folder 35)
  - Karpinski, Louis C., 1929-33 (Box 377, Folder 36)
  - Kaufman, F. Wilhelm, 1931-39 (Box 377, Folder 37)
  - Ke-Kei (misc), 1920-39 (Box 377, Folder 38)
  - Keeler, Edith Elizabeth '32, 1932-37; undated (Box 377, Folder 39)
  - Keiley, Anna Olivia ex '28 and parents, 1927 (Box 377, Folder 40)
  - Kel (misc), 1921-39; undated (Box 377, Folder 41)
  - Keller, Helen, 1927-36 (Box 377, Folder 42)
  - Kem-Kez (misc), 1920-39; undated (Box 378, Folder 1)
  - Kempton, Ella (von Tuyl) '02, 1928-32 (Box 378, Folder 2)
  - Kennedy, Clarence, 1918-39 (Box 378, Folder 3)
  - Kennedy, Ruth Lee, 1932-38 (Box 378, Folder 4)
  - Kennedy, Ruth Wedgwood, 1930-32 (Box 378, Folder 5)
  - Kenyon, Dorothy '08, 1925-39 (Box 378, Folder 6)
  - Keppel, F. P., 1924-34 (Box 378, Folder 7)
  - Kerns, S. K., 1924-39 (Box 378, Folder 8)
  - Ki (misc), 1920-39; undated (Box 378, Folder 9)
  - Kimball, Elizabeth (McGrew) '01, 1919-35 (Box 378, Folder 10)
  - Kimball, Elsa Peverly, 1929-36 (Box 378, Folder 11)
  - Kimball, Everett, 1918-36 (Box 378, Folder 12)
  - King, Franklin, 1917-34 (Box 378, Folder 13)
  - King, Helen Maxwell, 1918-20 (Box 378, Folder 14)
  - King, Henry H., 1926-38 (Box 378, Folder 15)
  - King, Stanley, 1924-38 (Box 378, Folder 16)
  - Kirk, Annett Ewing '30, 1929; undated (Box 378, Folder 17)
  - Kirkland, Winifred, 1925-31 (Box 378, Folder 18)
  - Kirstein, Louis E., 1923-39 (Box 378, Folder 19)
  - Kirstein, Mina Stein '18, 1919-28 (Box 378, Folder 20)
  - Kittredge, George Lyman, 1920-37 (Box 378, Folder 21)
  - Kl-Kn (misc), 1920-39 (Box 378, Folder 22)
  - Kluckhohn, Frank L., 1931-32 (Box 378, Folder 23)
  - Ko-Kz (misc), 1920-39; undated (Box 378, Folder 24)
  - Koch, Catharine Elizabeth, 1927-36 (Box 378, Folder 25)
  - Koch, Emma, 1925-28 (Box 378, Folder 26)
  - Koffka, Kurt, 1927-39 (Box 378, Folder 27)
  - Kohn, Hans, 1933-41 (Box 378, Folder 28)
  - Kotschnig, Walter M., 1936-39 (Box 378, Folder 29)
  - Kraushaar, Otto Frederick, 1933-39 (Box 378, Folder 30)
  - Kursheedt, Alphonse H., 1929-34 (Box 378, Folder 31)
  - Kyle, Anne Dempster '18, 1920-32 (Box 378, Folder 32)
  - Kynett, H. H. and Mary Elizabeth, 1935 (Box 378, Folder 33)
  - La-Lam (misc), 1922-39; undated (Box 378, Folder 34)
  - Lake, Kirsopp, 1920-34 (Box 378, Folder 35)
  - Lamont, Corliss, 1928-38 (Box 378, Folder 36)
  - Lamont, Florence (Corliss) '93, 1925-39; undated (Box 378, Folder 37)
  - Lamont, Thomas William, Sr., 1917-40 (Box 378, Folder 38-40)
  - Lan-Laz (misc), 1915-39; undated (Box 379, Folder 1)
  - Landis, J. N., 1922-39 (Box 379, Folder 2)
  - Lane, Alfred C., 1925-29 (Box 379, Folder 3)
  - Lane, Lillian Mary, 1920-28 (Box 379, Folder 4)
  - LaPiana, George, 1929-38 (Box 379, Folder 5)
  - Larkin, Oliver Waterman, 1927-39 (Box 379, Folder 6)
  - Laski, Harold J., 1931-36 (Box 379, Folder 7)
  - Lathrop, Adele, 1919-35 (Box 379, Folder 8)
  - Laughton, Lizbeth R., 1928-38 (Box 379, Folder 9)
  - Le-Lei (misc), 1917-39; undated (Box 379, Folder 10)
  - Leach, Henry Goddard, 1927-38 (Box 379, Folder 11)
  - Leary, Gertrude E., 1920-38 (Box 379, Folder 12)
  - Leary, Olga Cushing '26, 1925-30 (Box 379, Folder 13)
  - LeBoutillier, C. G., 1934-35 (Box 379, Folder 14)
  - Lee, Gerald Stanley, 1922-39; undated (Box 379, Folder 15-16)
  - Lee, Jennette (Perry) '86, 1921-40 (Box 379, Folder 17)
  - Leindecker, John P., 1936 (Box 379, Folder 18)
  - Leiper, Henry Smith, 1932-39 (Box 379, Folder 19)
  - Leiter, Hazel Belle ex '22, 1922 (Box 379, Folder 20)
  - Lel-Lez (misc), 1918-39; undated (Box 379, Folder 21)
  - Leland, Marine, 1929-36 (Box 379, Folder 22)
  - Lewis, B. Roland, 1928-38; undated (Box 379, Folder 23)
  - Lewis, Gertrude Maxton, 1925-26 (Box 379, Folder 24)
  - Ley, Harold A., 1928-29 (Box 379, Folder 25)
  - Li-Ll (misc), 1918-39; undated (Box 379, Folder 26)
  - Lichtenstein, Walter, 1921-27 (Box 379, Folder 27)
  - Lieder, Paul Robert, 1919-39 (Box 379, Folder 28)
  - Lind, Melva Elizabeth, 1929-35 (Box 379, Folder 29)
  - Lindbergh, Anne (Morrow) '28 and Charles A., 1935-43 (Box 379, Folder 30)
  - Lindeke, Albert W., Caroline (Saunders) '01, and Mary Proal '33, 1927-39 (Box 379, Folder 31)
  - Linehan, Mary De Lacy ex '84, 1920-25 (Box 379, Folder 32)
  - Lippman, Walter, 1928-37 (Box 379, Folder 33)
  - Lo-Lon (misc), 1923-39; undated (Box 379, Folder 34)
  - Locke, Arthur Ware, 1917-38 (Box 379, Folder 35)
  - Lodge, Henry Cabot, 1923-39 (Box 379, Folder 36)
  - Logan, Bertha (Allen) '95, 1920-37 (Box 379, Folder 37)
  - Long, Alice L., 1928-29; undated (Box 379, Folder 38)
  - Loo-Lu (misc), 1919-39; undated (Box 379, Folder 39)
  - Loomis, Clara Denison '00, 1922-30 (Box 379, Folder 40)
  - Lord, Eleanor Louisa '87, 1922-36 (Box 379, Folder 41)
  - Lovett, Sidney, 1927-35 (Box 379, Folder 42)
  - Lowell, A. Lawrence, 1919-26 (Box 379, Folder 43)
  - Lowenthal, Esther, 1918-39 (Box 379, Folder 44)
  - Lowes, John L., 1920-31 (Box 379, Folder 45)
  - Lumpkin, Katharine Du Pre, 1932-39 (Box 379, Folder 46)
  - Ly (misc), 1920-38 (Box 379, Folder 47)
  - Lyman, Frank, 1927-36 (Box 379, Folder 48)
  - Lyon, Helen L., 1935-39 (Box 379, Folder 49)
  - Ma-McB (misc), 1923-39; undated (Box 380, Folder 1)
  - McArdle, Florence, 1921-22; undated (Box 380, Folder 2)
  - McBee, Mary Vardrine '06, 1921-39 (Box 380, Folder 3)
  - McC (misc), 1918-39 (Box 380, Folder 4)
  - McCall, Samuel W., 1918-21 (Box 380, Folder 5)
  - McCallum, George Bliss, 1917-33 (Box 380, Folder 6)
  - McColley, Grant, 1937-39 (Box 380, Folder 7)
  - McCoy, Neal Henry, 1931 (Box 380, Folder 8)
  - McCracken, Mary H., 1925-26 (Box 380, Folder 9)
  - McD-McF (misc), 1920-39; undated (Box 380, Folder 10)
  - Macdonnell, J. S., 1925-37 (Box 380, Folder 11)
  - McElwain, Mary Belle, 1918-30 (Box 380, Folder 12)
  - Macfarland, Charles S., 1929-33 (Box 380, Folder 13)
  - McG-McK (misc), 1919-39; undated (Box 380, Folder 14)
  - Macgregor, Margaret Eliot, 1926-32 (Box 380, Folder 15)
  - McL-McZ (misc), 1920-39 (Box 380, Folder 16)
  - Macy, John, 1919-32 (Box 380, Folder 17)
  - Mad-Man (misc), 1918-39 (Box 380, Folder 18)
  - Magna, (Sarah) Edith (Scott) '09, 1927-39 (Box 380, Folder 19)
  - Maher, Amy Grace '06, 1918-35 (Box 380, Folder 20)
  - Mahoney, Walter B., 1925-30 (Box 380, Folder 21)
  - Malcolmson, Margaret (Wilkinson) '99, 1925-32 (Box 380, Folder 22)
  - Mandelbaum, Maurice H., 1925-26 (Box 380, Folder 23)
  - Mar (misc), 1921-39 (Box 380, Folder 24)
  - Marble, Annie (Russell) '86, 1919-36 (Box 380, Folder 25)
  - Marks, Percy, 1923-36 (Box 380, Folder 26)
  - Marsh, Lucille, 1921-25 (Box 380, Folder 27)
  - Marsh, Margaret (Alexander) '14, 1929-33 (Box 380, Folder 28)
  - Marsh, Marie B., 1925-28 (Box 380, Folder 29)
  - Martin, Gertrude Belle ex '20, 1920-38 (Box 380, Folder 30)
  - Marx, Erich, 1933-34 (Box 380, Folder 31)
  - Mas-Maz (misc), 1918-39 (Box 380, Folder 32)
  - Mason, Jennie H., 1929; undated (Box 380, Folder 33)
  - Matlack, Judith, 1920-27 (Box 380, Folder 34)
  - Mattison, Mary Dale '31, 1931-32 (Box 380, Folder 35)
  - Me (misc), 1918-40 (Box 380, Folder 36)
  - Mensel, Ernst Heinrich, 1920-33 (Box 380, Folder 37)
  - Meredith, Florence, 1923-27 (Box 380, Folder 38)
  - Meyerhoff, Howard Augustus, 1926-39 (Box 380, Folder 39-42)
  - Mi-Mj (misc), 1921-39; undated (Box 381, Folder 1)
  - Michaud, Regis, 1917-20 (Box 381, Folder 2)
  - Miller, Dickinson Sergeant, 1923-33 (Box 381, Folder 3)
  - Miller, William John, 1917-24 (Box 381, Folder 4)
  - Mirick, George A., 1925-35 (Box 381, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous, 1917-44; undated (Box 381, Folder 6)
  - Moa-Moo (misc), 1920-39 (Box 381, Folder 7)
  - Moog, Wilson Townsend, 1919-39 (Box 381, Folder 8)
  - Mor-Morr (misc), 1920-42 (Box 381, Folder 9)
  - Morgenthau, Mengo L., 1924-25 (Box 381, Folder 10)
  - Morize, Andre and Ruth, 1931-39 (Box 381, Folder 11)
  - Morrow, Dwight Whitney, 1919-33 (Box 381, Folder 12)
  - Morrow, Elizabeth (Cutter) '96, 1919-39 (Box 381, Folder 13-14)
  - Mors-Mz (misc), 1919-40 (Box 381, Folder 15)
  - Morse, Marjorie Dewey, Jr., 1932 (Box 381, Folder 16)
  - Morse, William R., 1922-28 (Box 381, Folder 17)
  - Morton, David, 1928-35 (Box 381, Folder 18)
  - Moulinet, Aline de Villele, 1922-40 (Box 381, Folder 19)
  - Muchnic, Helen, 1928-39 (Box 381, Folder 20)
  - Murfin, Winifred Anne '26, 1926 (Box 381, Folder 21)
  - Murphy, Eleanor ex '20, 1917-18 (Box 381, Folder 22)
  - Murrow, Edward R., 1933-36 (Box 381, Folder 23)
  - Na (misc), 1927-39; undated (Box 381, Folder 24)
  - Nathan, Paul, 1935-38 (Box 381, Folder 25)
  - Ne (misc), 1920-39; undated (Box 381, Folder 26)
  - Neal, Josephine B., 1926-27 (Box 381, Folder 27)
  - Neely, Rachel Eve '30, 1929-43 (Box 381, Folder 28)
  - Neff, S. B., 1923-38 (Box 381, Folder 29)
  - Newell, Jane Isabel, 1918-31 (Box 381, Folder 30)
  - Ni (misc), 1920-41; undated (Box 382, Folder 1)
  - Nicholson, Marjorie Hope, 1923-39 (Box 382, Folder 2-3)
  - No-Nz (misc), 1918-39 (Box 382, Folder 4)
  - Norton, Charles D., 1920-22 (Box 382, Folder 5)
  - Norton, Elizabeth G., 1923 (Box 382, Folder 6)
  - Norton, Katherine (Garrison) '95, 1920-33; undated (Box 382, Folder 7)
  - Noyes, Helen McGregor, 1919-32 (Box 382, Folder 8)
  - O-Ol (misc), 1919-39 (Box 382, Folder 9)
  - Oak, Lura Sawyer, 1930-36 (Box 382, Folder 10)
  - O'Brien, Harriet Ellen '21, 1929-31 (Box 382, Folder 11)
  - O'Halloran, Beth (MacDuffie) '20, 1933 (Box 382, Folder 12)
  - Olander, Edwin L., 1935-38 (Box 382, Folder 13)
  - Oldham, John E., 1923-39 (Box 382, Folder 14)
  - Olmsted, Robert Elisha Stanley, 1919-26 (Box 382, Folder 15-16)
  - Om-Oz (misc), 1921-39; undated (Box 382, Folder 17)
  - O'Mara, Charlotte Anne ex '31, 1928-30 (Box 382, Folder 18)
  - Orton, William Aylotte, 1922-41 (Box 382, Folder 19)
  - Osgood, Hamilton and June, 1920-30 (Box 382, Folder 20)
  - Pa-Paq (misc), 1921-39; undated (Box 382, Folder 21)
  - Packard, Sidney Raymond, 1921-34 (Box 382, Folder 22)
  - Palmer, George Herbert, 1925-28 (Box 382, Folder 23)
  - Pangborn, H. L., 1925-32 (Box 382, Folder 24)
  - Pantling, Dorothie F., 1918-28 (Box 382, Folder 25)
  - Par-Paz (misc), 1916-39; undated (Box 382, Folder 26)
  - Park, Frances Fenton Bernard, 1928-39 (Box 382, Folder 27)
  - Park, Marian, 1922-39 (Box 382, Folder 28)
  - Parker, Alice Farwell '23, 1922-28; undated (Box 382, Folder 29)
  - Parker, William, 1921-34 (Box 382, Folder 30)
  - Parshley, Howrd Madison, 1921-39 (Box 382, Folder 31)
  - Parsons, Alice (Lord) '97, 1918-39 (Box 382, Folder 32-33)
  - Patch, Howard Rollin, 1917-39 (Box 382, Folder 34)
  - Paton, Jean Agnes '14, 1926-37 (Box 382, Folder 35)
  - Pe (misc), 1909-39; undated (Box 383, Folder 1)
  - Peck, Martin W., 1925 (Box 383, Folder 2)
  - Pelletier, Henriette, 1931-32 (Box 383, Folder 3)
  - Penn, Cordelia and Rucker, 1922 (Box 383, Folder 4)
  - Perkins, Elizabeth (Ward), 1925-26 (Box 383, Folder 5)
  - Perkins, James Handasyd, 1925-39 (Box 383, Folder 6)
  - Perry, Bliss, 1934-39 (Box 383, Folder 7)
  - Perry, Henry Ten Eyck, 1917-23 (Box 383, Folder 8)
  - Perry, Ralph Barton, 1924-38 (Box 383, Folder 9)
  - Peterson, Tellef C., 1921 (Box 383, Folder 10)
  - Pettengill, Rachel Thoyer and Ray W., 1921-26 (Box 383, Folder 11)
  - Ph-Pl (misc), 1919-39; undated (Box 383, Folder 12)
  - Piccoli, Raffaelo, 1919-33 (Box 383, Folder 13)
  - Pierce, Chauncey H., 1918-33 (Box 383, Folder 14)
  - Plimpton, Fanny (Hastings) '03, 1921-35 (Box 383, Folder 15)
  - Plimpton, George A., 1923-33 (Box 383, Folder 16)
  - Po (misc), 1917-42 (Box 383, Folder 17)
  - Poggioli, Renato, 1938-44 (Box 383, Folder 18)
  - Pope, Arthur, 1922-26 (Box 383, Folder 19)
  - Porteous, Alexander James Dow, 1926-36 (Box 383, Folder 20)
  - Post, Theodore H., 1919-24 (Box 383, Folder 21)
  - Potts, Abbie Findlay, 1923-34 (Box 383, Folder 22)
  - Pr (misc), 1921-39 (Box 383, Folder 23)
  - Prather, Elisabeth '27, 1926-32 (Box 383, Folder 24)
  - Prichard, Louise Gilman ex '21, 1921 (Box 383, Folder 25)
  - Pryor, Frances (Siviter) '10, 1928-32 (Box 383, Folder 26)
  - Pu-Q (misc), 1917-39 (Box 383, Folder 27)
  - Pyle, Adele Knight ex '29, 1926 (Box 383, Folder 28)
  - Ra (misc), 1920-39 (Box 383, Folder 29)
  - Rand, E. K., 1923-39 (Box 383, Folder 30)
  - Ratcliffe, S. K., 1920-42 (Box 383, Folder 31-32)
  - Re (misc), 1917-40; undated (Box 383, Folder 33)
  - Reed, Clara Norton, 1925-34 (Box 383, Folder 34)
  - Reid, W. T., 1923-27 (Box 383, Folder 35)
  - Rembaugh, Bertha, 1920-26 (Box 383, Folder 36)
  - Reynolds, Amelia S., 1922-25 (Box 383, Folder 37)
  - Reynolds, F. J., 1921-23 (Box 383, Folder 38)
  - Reynolds, James Bronson, 1923-24 (Box 383, Folder 39)
  - Rh-Ri (misc), 1917-38; undated (Box 383, Folder 40)
  - Rhees, Harriet (Seelye) '88, 1925-28 (Box 383, Folder 41)
  - Rice, Robert Ashley, 1919-39; undated (Box 383, Folder 42)
  - Richards, Elizabeth '18, 1919-20 (Box 383, Folder 43)
  - Richards, Laura E., 1902-35 (Box 383, Folder 44)
  - Richards, Katharine Lambert '13, 1928-33 (Box 383, Folder 45)
  - Richardson, Anna Mann, 1927-32 (Box 383, Folder 46)
  - Richter, Werner, 1918-39 (Box 383, Folder 47)
  - Riddle, C. B., 1922-23 (Box 383, Folder 48)
  - Ripley, William Z., 1920-29 (Box 383, Folder 49)
  - Roa-Rob (misc), 1919-39; undated (Box 384, Folder 1)
  - Robert, Osmond Thomas, 1918-35 (Box 384, Folder 2)
  - Robinson, James Harvey, 1924 (Box 384, Folder 3)
  - Robinson, Walter O., 1922-35 (Box 384, Folder 4)
  - Roc-Rog (misc), 1920-39; undated (Box 384, Folder 5)
  - Rogers, Agnes Low, 1923-28 (Box 384, Folder 6)
  - Rogers, David Camp, 1918-39 (Box 384, Folder 7)
  - Rogers, Elizabeth Frances, 1919-23 (Box 384, Folder 8)
  - Rol-Roz (misc), 1917-41 (Box 384, Folder 9)
  - Rollins, Hyder E., 1924-26 (Box 384, Folder 10)
  - Rooke, Margaret Le Breton, 1919-39 (Box 384, Folder 11)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor and Franklin Delano, 1932-40 (Box 384, Folder 12)
  - Ross, Clarence B., 1925 (Box 384, Folder 13)
  - Ross, Gilbert, 1935-39 (Box 384, Folder 14)
  - Rua-Rur (misc), 1920-38 (Box 384, Folder 15)
  - Ruben, Sylvia Fox ex '29, 1929-31 (Box 384, Folder 16)
  - Rus-Ruz (misc), 1920-39; undated (Box 384, Folder 17)
  - Russell, Louise '23, 1925 (Box 384, Folder 18)
  - Rypins, Stanley, 1922-38 (Box 384, Folder 19)
  - Sa (misc), 1922-39; undated (Box 384, Folder 20)
  - Sachs, Paul J., 1919-32 (Box 384, Folder 21)
  - Salvemini, Gaetano, 1931-38 (Box 384, Folder 22)
  - Sampson, Myra Melissa, 1919-39 (Box 384, Folder 23)
  - Sandford, M. E., 1921-22 (Box 384, Folder 24)
  - Sargent, Porter, 1922-39 (Box 384, Folder 25)